SHELDON:
Wait. I'm confused.
(Sheldon:)Why would you need
both a robot girlfriend
(Sheldon:)and a robot prostitute?
(Howard:)There's just some things
you don't do
(Howard:)with your robot girlfriend.
(Raj:)Boy, when you met Bernadette,
(Raj:)the field of robotics
really took a hit.
(Leonard:)Okay, let's just skip
(Leonard:)all the inventions
you can have sex with.
All right, no-- here we go:
"Ergonomic heated seat cushion."
(Howard:)No, it vibrates.
Keep going.
(Leonard:)You know, let's just come up
with something new.
SHELDON:
You know,
(Sheldon:)a number of significant
innovations have been inspired
(Sheldon:)by science fiction.
The-the geosynchronous satellite
from Arthur C. Clarke.
(Sheldon:)The Motorola flip phone--
that came from Star Trek.
Yeah, and I've long suspected
that the idea
(Sheldon:)of an African-American president
was stolen
from the movie Deep Impact.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey,
(Raj:)the future they show
in Back to the Future II